David Kloepper

dk@davidkloepper.com https://www.davidkloepper.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a working professional with over 8 years of experience in research and development and logistics. My diverse background in agricultural science and computer science, coupled with my hands-on experience in various roles, has equipped me with a unique skill set that allows me to solve a wide range of problems.

EDUCATION

Boise State University, Boise, ID

2021

• Completed courses in Computer Science in pursuit of a second B.S.

California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, CA

2009 - 2014

B.S. in Agricultural Science

• Minor in Agribusiness and Concentration in Agricultural Supplies and Services

EXPERIENCE

Fulfillment Center Associate

2022 - Present

- Trained dozens of new hires to work safely and efficiently in a large warehouse environment
- Cross-trained associates in additional process paths to maximize productivity
- Regularly receive documented positive feedback for performance, quality, and safety
- Completed the supplemental training which equipped me to troubleshoot problems with FC equipment
- Participated in Data Analytics training which expanded my skills in Excel, SQL, and Python

Regulatory Compliance Assistant

2018 - 2020

- Submitted pesticide research authorizations to CDPR for agricultural product development trials
- Communicated with County Ag Commissioners regarding notices of intent and experimental trial reports
- Took pictures of research trials using DJI Phantom 4 Pro drone with RGB and NDVI cameras
- Provided general support to the reporting team by performing data entry and generating reports
- Maintained safety stations (first aid, eye wash, and shower), fire extinguishers, and posted safety boards

Research Station Administrative Assistant

2016 - 2017

- Worked with research assistants to pack and ship envelopes of vegetable seeds worldwide
- Prepared customs invoices, packing lists, and certificates of origin for shipments of vegetable seeds
- Purchased shipping waybills daily and drove packages to Fedex/UPS/DHL drop offs or scheduled pickups
- Obtained Phytosanitary Certificates from Yolo County Weights & Measures for shipments
- Organized monthly safety meetings for 100+ employees, and scheduled guest visits and tours

Research Analyst Assistant

2014 - 2016

- Performed data entry and interacted with clients regarding data updates and trial status
- Generated MS Word and Excel reports for research and development trials
- Analyzed trial data using JMP11 and ARM statistical software packages
- Maintained weather stations with monthly data collections
- Maintained the company website, and prepared newsletters and marketing documents

SKILLS

- C, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, Markdown
- Visual Studio Code, git
- MS Office Suite, Google Docs, Looker Studio, Tableau
- R, SAS, MiniTab, JMP, ARM (by GDM)
- OBS, Audacity, OpenShot Video Editor, KDenLive, GIMP